{
    "subject": "resource/Paessler",
    "predicate": "ontology/product",
    "object": "resource/PRTG_Network_Monitor",
    "human_readable": "Paessler's product is PRTG Network Monitor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8408629894256592,
            "question": "What is the name of Paessler's network monitoring product?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8269983530044556,
            "question": "Who manufactures PRTG Network Monitor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7967486381530762,
            "question": "Does Paessler make other products besides PRTG?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7740219235420227,
            "question": "What does PRTG Network Monitor monitor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6937695741653442,
            "question": "What type of software is PRTG Network Monitor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6645104885101318,
            "question": "What could be a use case for PRTG Network Monitor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6288862228393555,
            "question": "Is PRTG a hardware or software product?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.609198808670044,
            "question": "What product does Paessler make?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5341768860816956,
            "question": "What industry is Paessler involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28743332624435425,
            "question": "What is Paessler known for developing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paessler's product is PRTG Network Monitor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6159_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industry is Paessler involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6159_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What product does Paessler make?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6159_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is PRTG a hardware or software product?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6159_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6159_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe document mentions \"Paessler PRTG Network Monitor\" several times, and it seems to be the main focus of the text. There are no contradictions or other information that would suggest otherwise. Therefore, based on this evidence, it appears that Paessler's product is indeed PRTG Network Monitor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Paessler's product is PRTG Network Monitor.\" Each document mentions PRTG Network Monitor as a product developed by Paessler AG, providing details about its features and capabilities."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}